

## SAGAR SINGH

TERRITORY SALES REPRESENTATIVE

PHONE-9198834888

EMAIL- SAGARSINGHLKO48@GMAIL.COM

# **PROFILE SUMMARY**

Currently working as, a TSR at Bosch, having an overall experience of 8 years in business management. Looking forward to growing my career with a company that promotes quality products and services and provides me with exposure and opportunities to meet and exceed assigned goals and targets.

Have a demonstrated history of responsible and sincere working in a deadline driven

#### **SKILLS**

- Sales Management
- New Business Development
- Innovative
- Service-focused
- good Communication
- Analytical Skills

## **ACTIVITIES AND INTERESTS**

Theater • Environmental conservation • Art • Singing • Travel

# **EXPERIENCE**

**Bosch Built-in Appliances/** Territory Sales Representative – UP East Jun 2020-Till Date

- Handling and helping Bosch meet the target sales and expanding their business in UP East.
- Achieved sales of 1Cr against a given target of 70 Lakhs.

#### Acrysil Ltd/ Area Sales Manager - UP East

Jun 2016 - Jun 2020

- Handled the sales of Building material of modular kitchen based sinks & built in appliances.
- Achieved aggressive targets.
- Worked in a deadline driven environment.

#### Bell Laminates / Sales Executive - UP East

Jul 2015 - May 2016

- Helped and expanded sales of laminates in the region of UP East & surrounding areas.
- Achieved aggressive targets.
- Showed a character of discipline and sincerity.

#### **EDUCATION**

- Symbiosis Center for Distance Learning / PGDBA
  Jan 2022 Jan 2024
- Kanpur University/ BSC

Apr 2012 - Aug 2015, Kanpur

• RDKIC Hardoi/ SSC in Sciences

Apr 2011 - Mar 2012

Mahatma Gandhi Montessori Inter college

Apr 2007 - Mar 2008

## **ACCOMPLISHMENTS**

- Achieved sales of 1Cr against a given target of 70 Lakhs in Bosch.
- Achieved sales target of 100 % for 4 consecutive years in Acrysil.
- Achieved target sales of 70 % in Bell laminates with full dealer and customer satisfaction.

